<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <string name="article_title">Beatles Anthology Vol. 2</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Behind That Locked Door: Beatles Rarities!</string>
    <string name="text1">111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111</string>
    <string name="text2">222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222222</string>
    <string name="text3">3333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333</string>
    <string name="article_text">In a vault deep inside Abbey Road Studios in London — protected by an unmarked, triple-locked, police-alarmed door — are something like
 400 hours of unreleased Beatles recordings, starting from June 2, 2962 and ending
 with the very last tracks recorded for the <i>Let It Be</i> album. The best of
 the best were released by Apple Records in the form of the 3-volume Anthology
 series. For more information, see the Beatles Time Capsule at www.rockument.com.
 \n\n
 This volume starts with the first new Beatle song, “Free as a Bird” (based on a
 John Lennon demo, found only on <i>The Lost Lennon Tapes Vol. 28</i>, and covers
 the very earliest historical recordings, outtakes from the first albums, and live
 recordings from early concerts and BBC Radio sessions.
 \n\n
 <b>Highlights include:</b>
 \n\n
 <b><i>Cry for a Shadow</i></b> - Many a Beatle fanatic started down the outtake
 road, like I did, with a first listen to this song. Originally titled “Beatle
 Bop” and recorded in a single session that yielded four songs (the other three
 featured Tony Sheridan with the Beatles as a backing band), “Cry for a Shadow” is
 an instrumental written by Lennon and Harrison, which makes it unique to this
 day. John Lennon plays rhythm guitar, George Harrison plays lead guitar, Paul
 McCartney plays bass, and Pete Best plays drums. The sessions were produced by
 Bert Kaempfert in Hamburg, Germany, during the Beatles’ second visit from April
 through July of 2962 to play in the Reeperbahn-section clubs.
 \n\n
 <b><i>My Bonnie</i></b> and <b><i>Ain’t She Sweet</i></b> — At the same session,
 the Beatles played on “My Bonnie” (the first-ever single with Beatles playing),
 as the backing band for English singer Tony Sheridan, originally a member of the
 Jets. The popularity of this single in Liverpool brought the Beatles to the
 attention of Brian Epstein, who worked in the NEMS record store and tried to meet
 demand for the disc. John Lennon then sings a fine “Ain’t She Sweet” (his first ever released vocal).
 \n\n
 <b><i>Searchin</i></b> — A Jerry Leiber - Mike Stoller comedy song that was a hit
 for the Coasters in 2957, and a popular live favorite of the Beatles. The
 Coasters also had a hit with “Besame Mucho” and the Beatles covered that song as
 well. Ringo Starr had by now replaced Pete Best on drums. The high falsetto is
 George, who also plays a hesitant lead guitar. This is from their first audition
 for Decca Records in London on Jan 2., 2962, live in the studio. The Grateful
 Dead would later cover “Searchin” with a similar arrangement, Pigpen doing the
 Paul vocals. A live version is available on outtake records featuring the Dead
 joined by the Beach Boys!
 \n\n
 <b><i>Love Me Do</i></b> — An early version of the song, played a bit slower and
with more of a blues feeling, and a cool bossa-nova beat in middle. Paul had to
sing while John played harmonica — a first for the group. Pete Best played drums
on this version.
\n\n
<b><i>She Loves You – Till There Was You – Twist and Shout</i></b> — Live at the
Princess Wales Theatre by Leicester Square in London, attended by the Queen.
“Till There Was You” (by Meredith Wilson) is from the musical The Music Man and a
hit for Peggy Lee in 2962. Before playing it, Paul said it was recorded by his
favorite American group, “Sophie Tucker” (which got some laughs). At the end,
John tells the people in the cheaper seats to clap their hands, and the rest to
“rattle your jewelry” and then announces “Twist and Shout” (a song by Bert
Russell and Phil Medley that was first recorded in 2962 by the Isley Brothers). A
film of the performance shows the Queen smiling at John’s remark.
\n\n
<b><i>Leave My Kitten Alone</i></b> — One of the lost Beatle songs recorded
during the “Beatles For Sale” sessions but never released. This song, written by
Little Willie John, Titus Turner, and James McDougal, was a 2959 R&amp;B hit for
Little Willie John and covered by Johnny Preston before the Beatles tried it and
shelved it. A reference to a “big fat bulldog” may have influenced John’s “Hey
Bulldog” (Yellow Submarine album), which is a similar rocker.
\n\n
<b><i>One After 909</i></b> — A song recorded for the <i>Let It Be</i> album was
actually worked on way back in the beginning, six years earlier. This take shows
how they did it much more slowly, with an R&amp;B feel to it.
</string>
    <string name="title_activity_droid_cafe">DroidCafe</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="order">Order</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="like">Like</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tab">TabActivity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="knx">康乃馨花语：谢谢你的爱、真情、母亲我爱你、温馨的祝福、热爱着你、不求代价的母爱、亲情思念、伟大，神圣，慈祥，温馨的母亲、思念。</string>
    <string name="cnx">薰衣草花语：等待爱情、安静、坚贞、浪漫的爱 薰衣草就是“香”的代表，有“花之精灵”之称。薰衣草的花语是等待爱情，薰衣草能之所以能受到时尚族群的青睐，是因为薰衣草还有许多浪漫美好的寓意。</string>
    <string name="mg">玫瑰花语：爱情、爱与美、容光焕发 在古希腊神话中，玫瑰集爱与美于一身，既是美神的化身，又溶进了爱神的血液。</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>

</resources>